Muhammad Rizwan



About

I'mMhammad Rizwan,a seasoned professional with two years of expertise in Amazon FBA, specializing in wholesale and retail arbitrage. Additionally, I bring handson experience in TargetTo-Sell (TTS) and Walmart operations in the United States. I am confident that my skills and insights can contribute significantly to your organization.

Work Experience

Mirza Shopping center 2018-2019

Start working as a sales representative in own family shopping center

Network marketing 2019-2020

Worked as network marketer with USA based company FLP Limited.

Call agent 2020-2021

Worked as call agent at MKT call centre

Truck dispatching 2021-22

Worked as dispatcher at superoid tech.

CEO OF Oxolify LLC and Qalbi store LLC in Florida on Amazon.2023-24

Education

PGC Nankana sahib 2019-21

Intermediate degree Premedical.

Univesity of central punjab Lahore

Associate degree in sciences 2021–23

Skills

■■■■ Critical Thinking

■■■■ Problem Solving

■■■■ Communication

PHONE

+92 3090338359

WEBSITE

https://oxolify.com

MAIL

0123mrm456789@gmail.com

ADDRESS

house no.105 Habib homes peco road,Lahore